<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>zhixian's site</title><link>https://zhixian.io/en/</link><description>Recent content on zhixian's site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>© 2026 zhixian</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zhixian.io/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ClawPal: No More Hand-Editing JSON for Your AI Agent 🦞</title><link>https://zhixian.io/en/posts/clawpal-tutorial/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhixian.io/en/posts/clawpal-tutorial/</guid><description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ever asked your AI agent to modify its own config, only to watch it break itself? Then you spent an hour fixing it? Ever wanted a multi-agent Discord setup but couldn&amp;rsquo;t get the config right no matter how many tutorials you read?&lt;/p&gt;</description><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://zhixian.io/posts/clawpal-tutorial/cover.png"/></item><item><title>Advanced Agent Training: Multi-Agent Configuration in OpenClaw</title><link>https://zhixian.io/en/posts/agent-trainer-multi-agent-config/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhixian.io/en/posts/agent-trainer-multi-agent-config/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;After several days of intense work, I finally finished &lt;a href="https://botdrop.app" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;botdrop.app&lt;/a&gt;—a tool for running OpenClaw on Android—and now I have time to fill in some gaps. Have you been finding new ways to play with your 🦞 lately? I feel like this wave has truly spread everywhere; even friends who normally don&amp;rsquo;t care about tech are asking me about it.&lt;/p&gt;</description><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://zhixian.io/posts/agent-trainer-multi-agent-config/cover.png"/></item><item><title>认知有县 Podcast</title><link/><pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid/><description>&lt;p&gt;Sharing ideas, exploring new products, occasional conversations with friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://apple.co/4ay0hDL" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;Apple Podcast&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/34rYkRrG5UzceVS6Sxet1l" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer"&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Agent Trainer Advanced Guide: Building an Efficient OpenClaw Collaboration System with Discord</title><link>https://zhixian.io/en/posts/agent-trainer-discord-guide/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhixian.io/en/posts/agent-trainer-discord-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The promised second tutorial is here. In just a few days since my last update, Moltbot has renamed itself again—the pace of the AI era is truly relentless. Even faster than the name changes is the wave sparked by moltbook, with all kinds of agent-oriented products emerging left and right, opening my mind to the early shape of a new era. But let&amp;rsquo;s not get into that today; let me first fill in the gaps from before and share my experience and insights on using OpenClaw through Telegram and Discord.&lt;/p&gt;</description><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://zhixian.io/posts/agent-trainer-discord-guide/cover.png"/></item><item><title>BotDrop</title><link/><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid/><description>&lt;p&gt;Turn your old Android phone into an AI Agent server. Run your private AI assistant at zero cost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zero infrastructure cost — use hardware you already have&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Always with you — your agent lives where you live&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;True ownership — your data stays on your device&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Agent Trainer Case Study: Building Your Own Writing Workflow with Clawdbot</title><link>https://zhixian.io/en/posts/agent-trainer-writing-workflow/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhixian.io/en/posts/agent-trainer-writing-workflow/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;With Clawdbot&amp;rsquo;s rebranding to @moltbot, the initial excitement has started to fade. I wonder how many people have drifted back to their daily lives, and how many have stayed behind as &amp;ldquo;new species&amp;rdquo; left by the receding tide, ready to explore this new continent.&lt;/p&gt;</description><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://zhixian.io/posts/agent-trainer-writing-workflow/cover-generation-flow.jpg"/></item><item><title>Agent Trainer Security Class: Clawdbot 7-Step Self-Check Guide</title><link>https://zhixian.io/en/posts/agent-trainer-security-clawdbot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhixian.io/en/posts/agent-trainer-security-clawdbot/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;It feels like AI enthusiasts have been on an emotional roller coaster these past few days:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, they heard about something called Clawdbot—looks like a lobster?—and thought: What is this? Why is everyone sharing it? Why don&amp;rsquo;t I have it yet? So they frantically read articles and ordered a Mac mini. Then came the analysis posts saying this thing is extremely dangerous, has way too many permissions, absolutely terrifying—uninstall it now! So everyone nervously uninstalled, shut down, wiped their systems, and listed their machines on secondhand markets (maybe the 🦞 got sold too, haha).&lt;/p&gt;</description><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://zhixian.io/posts/agent-trainer-security-clawdbot/cover.png"/></item><item><title>Agent Trainer's Guide: Clawdbot Setup &amp; Lessons Learned</title><link>https://zhixian.io/en/posts/agent-trainer-guide-clawdbot/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhixian.io/en/posts/agent-trainer-guide-clawdbot/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Clawdbot suddenly blew up recently, which I find both surprising and inevitable. I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Clawdbot for three weeks now, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been incredibly excited every single day because it genuinely feels like science fiction has become reality. Friends who follow me probably noticed I was pretty hyped those first few days—and those who chatted with me definitely felt it, haha.&lt;/p&gt;</description><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://zhixian.io/posts/agent-trainer-guide-clawdbot/cover.png"/></item><item><title>Add a Local “Editor” to Whisper: Cleaning Transcripts with Apple Foundation Model</title><link>https://zhixian.io/en/posts/whisper-afm-refine/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 17:15:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://zhixian.io/en/posts/whisper-afm-refine/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;If you use voice-to-text often, you already know the problem: Whisper transcripts are usually not ready to ship. You get filler words, no punctuation, and sentences that run forever. You can either fix it manually, or you accept something that looks like a raw dump.&lt;/p&gt;</description><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://zhixian.io/posts/whisper-afm-refine/cover.png"/></item><item><title>Free Ride on Apple Intelligence: Turn macOS Built-in Model into an OpenAI API</title><link>https://zhixian.io/en/posts/apple-foundation-model-local-api/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 13:20:00 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://zhixian.io/en/posts/apple-foundation-model-local-api/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;macOS 26 Tahoe ships with a 3B parameter language model that Apple calls the Foundation Model. It normally hides in the system powering Writing Tools, Siri, and other features, but you can actually pull it out, wrap it as an OpenAI-compatible API, and plug it into any tool that supports the OpenAI format.&lt;/p&gt;</description><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://zhixian.io/posts/apple-foundation-model-local-api/cover.png"/></item><item><title>My "Doomsday Cabin": Building an AI Workbench with Discord</title><link>https://zhixian.io/en/posts/discord-ai-workspace/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 09:19:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhixian.io/en/posts/discord-ai-workspace/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re someone actively exploring the AI era, you should have your own Discord Server.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I call my Discord Server the &amp;ldquo;Doomsday Cabin.&amp;rdquo; The name might sound a bit dramatic, but it&amp;rsquo;s genuinely my most relied-upon work environment right now. &amp;ldquo;Doomsday&amp;rdquo; is a mental anchor I set for myself—the imagery helps me imagine being in the quiet of a wilderness, having one place I know still works, storing everything important to me. No matter how noisy or fast-changing things get outside, I still have a quiet place to continue working, thinking, and iterating.&lt;/p&gt;</description><media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://zhixian.io/posts/discord-ai-workspace/cover.jpg"/></item><item><title>From Looped Models (Ouro) to NVIDIA Rubin: Convergent Paths in the Inference Era</title><link>https://zhixian.io/en/posts/ouro-rubin-test-time-scaling/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 11:20:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhixian.io/en/posts/ouro-rubin-test-time-scaling/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;For the past few years, the story of AI getting stronger has been straightforward: throw more training compute at it, feed it more data, make the model bigger. Think of it as reading more books and doing more practice problems—cramming capability into parameters during training. But recently, the winds may be shifting: a model doesn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily need to keep growing; as long as it &amp;ldquo;thinks a bit longer&amp;rdquo; when facing hard problems, results can improve significantly.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>OwliaBot</title><link/><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid/><description>&lt;p&gt;Secure crypto-native AI Agent with built-in wallet solution and key isolation design.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Key &amp;amp; Agent Process Isolation — keys unreachable even under RCE&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sign Tier Risk Control — approval thresholds based on amount and frequency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Narrowed Execution Environment — command allowlist, no shell exec&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>Crypto UX Security Is Broken By Design</title><link>https://zhixian.io/en/posts/crypto-ux-security/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 14:26:40 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://zhixian.io/en/posts/crypto-ux-security/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;You wouldn&amp;rsquo;t wire $50,000 through a random website you found via Google ad. Yet that&amp;rsquo;s exactly what crypto wallets ask you to do every day—except when it goes wrong, there&amp;rsquo;s no bank to reverse the transaction, no fraud department to call, no chargeback to file.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Rediscovering Peace of Mind in DeFi: The Design Principles Behind Owlia</title><link>https://zhixian.io/en/posts/introduce-owlia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 22:38:39 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://zhixian.io/en/posts/introduce-owlia/</guid><description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;DeFi has become more powerful, but also more complex.&lt;br&gt;
Users are not lacking tools — they are lacking a partner who can carry some of the burden.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the past months, my team and I have been working on something I believe is deeply important:
an Agent that can genuinely accompany you in the DeFi world — &lt;strong&gt;Owlia&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Glossary of Web3 Account</title><link>https://zhixian.io/en/posts/web3-account-concepts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 20:09:28 +0900</pubDate><guid>https://zhixian.io/en/posts/web3-account-concepts/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;One of the most talked-about subjects at DevCon was account abstraction. Recently, you may have noticed acronyms and abbreviations like AA, EOA, SCW, and 4337 in a variety of presentations, panels, and streams. After reading these two sentence
s, your brain must already be hurting. Next, I&amp;rsquo;ll try to help you figure out what all these terms and ideas really mean.
This article is not a serious technical document, so it may use words that aren&amp;rsquo;t exact but are easy to understand. You are invited to use it as a starting point to learn more about these technologies.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>