<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>OpenClaw on zhixian&#39;s site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/en/tags/openclaw/</link>
    <description>Recent content in OpenClaw on zhixian&#39;s site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© 2026 zhixian</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/en/tags/openclaw/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>ClawPal: No More Hand-Editing JSON for Your AI Agent 🦞</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/clawpal-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/clawpal-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ever asked your AI agent to modify its own config, only to watch it break itself? Then you spent an hour fixing it? Ever wanted a multi-agent Discord setup but couldn&amp;rsquo;t get the config right no matter how many tutorials you read?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:1313/posts/clawpal-tutorial/cover.png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Agent Training: Multi-Agent Configuration in OpenClaw</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/agent-trainer-multi-agent-config/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/agent-trainer-multi-agent-config/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After several days of intense work, I finally finished &lt;a href=&#34;https://botdrop.app&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer&#34;&gt;botdrop.app&lt;/a&gt;—a tool for running OpenClaw on Android—and now I have time to fill in some gaps. Have you been finding new ways to play with your 🦞 lately? I feel like this wave has truly spread everywhere; even friends who normally don&amp;rsquo;t care about tech are asking me about it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:1313/posts/agent-trainer-multi-agent-config/cover.png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agent Trainer Advanced Guide: Building an Efficient OpenClaw Collaboration System with Discord</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/agent-trainer-discord-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/en/posts/agent-trainer-discord-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The promised second tutorial is here. In just a few days since my last update, Moltbot has renamed itself again—the pace of the AI era is truly relentless. Even faster than the name changes is the wave sparked by moltbook, with all kinds of agent-oriented products emerging left and right, opening my mind to the early shape of a new era. But let&amp;rsquo;s not get into that today; let me first fill in the gaps from before and share my experience and insights on using OpenClaw through Telegram and Discord.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <media:content xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:1313/posts/agent-trainer-discord-guide/cover.png" />
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
